<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
    <rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
        <channel>
        <atom:link href="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/litlitlitlit.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
            <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT</title>
            <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT is a bi-monthly literary event in Vancouver, BC that simply invites FOUR writers, poets and/or artists at a time to read their work to interested parties. LIT LIT LIT LIT is organized by Steffanie Ling and Emma Metcalfe Hurst.</description>
            <link>http://lit-lit-lit-lit.tumblr.com</link>
            <language>en-ca</language>
            <copyright>Creative Commons</copyright>
            <lastBuildDate>Mon, 5 Jun 2017 21:33:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 19:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
            <webMaster>elizibin@gmail.com</webMaster>
            <itunes:author>Produced by Emma Metcalfe Hurst and Steffanie Ling</itunes:author>
            <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT is a bi-monthly literary event in Vancouver, BC that simply invites FOUR writers, poets and/or artists at a time to read their work to interested parties.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT is a bi-monthly literary event in Vancouver, BC that simply invites FOUR writers, poets and/or artists at a time to read their work to interested parties. LIT LIT LIT LIT is organized by Steffanie Ling and Emma Metcalfe Hurst.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:owner>
                <itunes:name>Emma M H</itunes:name>
                <itunes:email>emmametcalfehurst@gmail.com</itunes:email>
            </itunes:owner>
            <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:image href="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/img/dulcelitbig.jpg" />
            <itunes:category text="Arts">
                <itunes:category text="Literature" />
            </itunes:category>
            <!-- Begin Items -->
            <item>

<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
              <!-- LIT I PART I -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT I - Part I: Zebulon Zang and Kara Hansen</title>
                <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT1P1.mp3</link>
                <guid>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT1P1.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Avenue 165 East Hastings St. Vancouver BC - Zebulon Zang, Kara Hansen, Alex Bovril, and Steffanie Ling. April 18th 2015 8:00pm. Asked to write a biography to accompany a reading, the writer can’t think of anything to write about himself. Does he give the names of cities, institutions, achievements? What achievements? He steps out for fresh air. During, a car (on which the painter’s ladders are piled) drives up. The writer asks the painter for help with the biography and the painter agrees, but they end up talking only about window cleaning. The painter wishes he could write: when you do condos you’re cleaning these windows that take, like, half a minute, and all day long briefly glimpsing hundreds of bedrooms, which is to say of hundreds of unconnected lives—or lives that just seemed unconnected but which in writing could take on connections—the painter gets to thinking. They finish enjoying the fresh air and part ways, the writer still not knowing what to say about himself. For now, Alex Bovril is a writer currently based in New York. Kara Hansen is an artist and writer living in Nanaimo and based in Vancouver. Currently she holds the position of Curatorial Intern at the Nanaimo Art Gallery. She and Jesse Birch are co-curating an exhibition entitled Spirit Gum at the Nanaimo Art Gallery come May. From time to time she bribes the karaoke guy with flowers for two songs instead of one. Steffanie Ling is a writer, curator and editor. She will have red wine and turtlenecks all year long. For LIT LIT LIT LIT she will be reading from work in process, tentatively titled “You’re a liar and a smoker” a book of twenty chapters for twenty cigarettes. Zebulon Zang is a filmmaker and writer from Maillardville, British Columbia. He is also the founder of the Maillardville Cultural Appreciation Society, an exhibition space dedicated to the promotion of culture in peripheral zones.</description>
                <enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT1P1.mp3" length="34192606" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Thu, 5 Nov 2015 11:44:01 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT I - Part 1: New readings written and given by Zebulon Zang, Kara Hansen. </itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT I - Part 1: Zebulon Zang and Kara Hansen:
LIT LIT LIT LIT I took place at Avenue  in Vancouver BC on April 18th, 2015. New readings were written and given by
Zebulon Zang, Kara Hansen, Alex Bovril and Steffanie Ling.

Kara Hansen’s reading “I’d Hurt A Fly, I Don’t Care If I Kill A Fly, I’d Kill A Fly“ and
Steffanie Ling’s reading “Clean Indoor Air Act (Act 1 and 2 of 3)“ are available as limited edition chap books, published and distributed by the Somewhat Urgent Series Press. </itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:49:32</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>

<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
            <!-- LIT I PART II  -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

             <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT I - Part II: Alex Bovril and Steffanie Ling</title>
                <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT1P2.mp3</link>
                <guid>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT1P2.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Avenue 165 East Hastings St. Vancouver BC - Zebulon Zang, Kara Hansen, Alex Bovril, and Steffanie Ling. April 18th 2015 8:00pm. Asked to write a biography to accompany a reading, the writer can’t think of anything to write about himself. Does he give the names of cities, institutions, achievements? What achievements? He steps out for fresh air. During, a car (on which the painter’s ladders are piled) drives up. The writer asks the painter for help with the biography and the painter agrees, but they end up talking only about window cleaning. The painter wishes he could write: when you do condos you’re cleaning these windows that take, like, half a minute, and all day long briefly glimpsing hundreds of bedrooms, which is to say of hundreds of unconnected lives—or lives that just seemed unconnected but which in writing could take on connections—the painter gets to thinking. They finish enjoying the fresh air and part ways, the writer still not knowing what to say about himself. For now, Alex Bovril is a writer currently based in New York. Kara Hansen is an artist and writer living in Nanaimo and based in Vancouver. Currently she holds the position of Curatorial Intern at the Nanaimo Art Gallery. She and Jesse Birch are co-curating an exhibition entitled Spirit Gum at the Nanaimo Art Gallery come May. From time to time she bribes the karaoke guy with flowers for two songs instead of one. Steffanie Ling is a writer, curator and editor. She will have red wine and turtlenecks all year long. For LIT LIT LIT LIT she will be reading from work in process, tentatively titled “You’re a liar and a smoker” a book of twenty chapters for twenty cigarettes. Zebulon Zang is a filmmaker and writer from Maillardville, British Columbia. He is also the founder of the Maillardville Cultural Appreciation Society, an exhibition space dedicated to the promotion of culture in peripheral zones.</description>
                <enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT1P2.mp3" length="42032885" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Thu, 5 Nov 2015 11:45:01 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT I - Part 2: New readings written and given by Alex Bovril and Steffanie Ling </itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT I - Part 2: Alex Bovril and Steffanie Ling:
LIT LIT LIT LIT I took place at Avenue in Vancouver BC on April 18th, 2015. New readings were written and given by Zebulon Zang, Kara Hansen, Alex Bovril and Steffanie Ling. Kara Hansen’s reading “I’d Hurt A Fly, I Don’t Care If I Kill A Fly, I’d Kill A Fly“ and Steffanie Ling’s reading “Clean Indoor Air Act (Act 1 and 2 of 3)“ are available as limited edition chap books, published and distributed by the Somewhat Urgent Series Press. </itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>01:36:00</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>

<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- LIT KIOSK I -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
            <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT KIOSK - Alex Bovril, Ingrid Olauson and Steffanie Ling</title>
                <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITKIOSK.mp3</link>
                <guid>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITKIOSK.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT KIOSK took place at Avenue in Vancouver BC on April 19, 2015 as a part of KIOSK, a reading room installation
curated by ddoogg. New readings were written and given by Alex Bovril, Ingrid Olauson and Steffanie Ling. </description>
                <enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITKIOSK.mp3" length="28298621" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Thu, 5 Nov 2015 11:46:01 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT KIOSK - New readings written and given by Alex Bovril, Ingrid Olauson and Steffanie Ling.</itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT KIOSK - Alex Bovril, Ingrid Olauson and Steffanie Ling
LIT LIT LIT LIT KIOSK took place at Avenue in Vancouver BC on April 19, 2015 as a part of KIOSK, a reading room installation curated by ddoogg. New readings were written and given by Alex Bovril, Ingrid Olauson and Steffanie Ling.</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:39:32</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>

<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
            <!-- LIT II PART I -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

            <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT II - Part I: Ronan Nanning-Watson and Zuzia Juszkiewicz</title>
                <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT2P1.mp3</link>
                <guid>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT2P1.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Publication Studio: 222 E Georgia St. Vancouver BC - Bradley Iles is reading from Derby: A Poem in Six Parts, a recent collaboration with Katrina Niebergal. Reincarnation, celebrity, the nature of the self, the selfhood of nature, Mustang-transcendentalism, a poem about a movie. Bradley lives on Melville street in Vancouver. Zuzia Juszkiewicz is a fragment in some kind of multi-faceted hybrid zone or something. She was born in Gdansk, and raised in South Africa, New Zealand, and Canada. She holds a BA in Visual Arts (Vancouver), Human Geography (Vancouver) and Urbanism at AHK (Amsterdam). She collaborates with writers, musicians, filmmakers and dancers. She often works under the name Modern Catalyst, with a focus on designing cross-disciplined artists.http://modercatalyst.ca . Ronan K. Nanning-Watson is a filmmaker, writer and artist from British Columbia. His work ranges in scope, medium, and aesthetic, but is consistently uncompromising. Recently he finished his first feature film “Crusade” about a group of young hipsters who start a holy war. The next two parts in the trilogy are in preproduction. Ingrid Olauson is a writer and trawler of people’s lives. She recently wrote, produced and acted in the play and collaborative art piece Fort Eff, which debuted at Deep Blue this past May. </description>
                <enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT2P1.mp3" length="30528110" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Thu, 5 Nov 2015 11:47:01 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT II - Part I: New readings written and given by Ronan Nanning-Watson, Zuzia Juszkiewicz.</itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT II - Part 1: Ronan Nanning-Watson and Zuzia Juszkiewickz
LIT LIT LIT LIT II took place at Publication Studio in Vancouver BC on June 28, 2015. New readings were written and given by Ronan Nanning-Watson, Zuzia Juszkiewicz, Bradley Iles and Ingrid Olauson.</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:43:02</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
            <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT II PART II -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
            <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT II - Part II: Bradley Iles and Ingrid Olauson</title>
                <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT2P2.mp3</link>
                <guid>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT2P2.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Publication Studio: 222 E Georgia St. Vancouver BC - Bradley Iles is reading from Derby: A Poem in Six Parts,a recent collaboration with Katrina Niebergal. Reincarnation, celebrity, the nature of the self, the selfhood of nature, Mustang-transcendentalism, a poem about a movie. Bradley lives on Melville street in Vancouver. Zuzia Juszkiewicz is a fragment in some kind of multi-faceted hybrid zone or something. She was born in Gdansk, and raised in South Africa, New Zealand, and Canada. She holds a BA in Visual Arts (Vancouver), Human Geography (Vancouver) and Urbanism at AHK (Amsterdam). She collaborates with writers, musicians, filmmakers and dancers. She often works under the name Modern Catalyst, with a focus on designing cross-disciplined artists.http://modercatalyst.ca . Ronan K. Nanning-Watson is a filmmaker, writer and artist from British Columbia. His work ranges in scope, medium, and aesthetic, but is consistently uncompromising. Recently he finished his first feature film “Crusade” about a group of young hipsters who start a holy war. The next two parts in the trilogy are in preproduction. Ingrid Olauson is a writer and trawler of people’s lives. She recently wrote, produced and acted in the play and collaborative art piece Fort Eff, which debuted at Deep Blue this past May. </description>
                <enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT2P2.mp3" length="30381379" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Thu, 5 Nov 2015 11:48:02 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT II - Part 2: New readings written and given by Bradley Iles and Ingrid Olauson.</itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT II - Part 2: Bradley Iles and Ingrid Olauson
LIT LIT LIT LIT II took place at Publication Studio in Vancouver BC on June 28, 2015. New readings written and given by Ronan Nanning-Watson, Zuzia Juszkiewicz, Bradley Iles and Ingrid Olauson.</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:42:45</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>

<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
            <!-- LIT III PART I -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

               <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT III - Part I: Maia Nichols and Alex Bovril </title>
                <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT3P1.mp3</link>
                <guid>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT3P1.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Publication Studio: 222 E Georgia St. Vancouver BC - ALEX BOVRIL is a writer and visual artist. Recently, he has been pouring colours of concrete and writing fiction. He is currently an MFA Candidate in Creative Writing at New York University.

DONATO MANCINI makes visual and procedural poetry, bookworks, and visual art. His books and chapbooks include: Snowline (2015), Buffet World (2011) Fact ‘N’ Value (2011), Hell Passport no.22 (2008), Æthel (2007), 58 Free Coffees (2006) and Ligatures (2005). Mancini’s published critical writing includes work on the archive, time and memory in Anamnesia: Unforgetting (2011), and a discourse analysis of poetry reviews in You Must Work Harder to Write Poetry of Excellence (2012). His most recent full length book, Loitersack (2014), is a labyrinthine commonplace book where critical, theoretical and para-literary tendencies intersect in the forms of poetry, poetics, theory, theory theatre, laugh particles and many many questions.

KATE MOSS is an Australian artist who works with drawing, writing, painting, sculpture, sound and performance. Her works explore the possibilities of conversation through the vernacular of landscape, rhythm and material experimentation.

MAIA NICHOLS (b. Berkeley, California) is an artist and writer. She holds a BA in Psychology and a BFA from the University of British Columbia. She is a Masters Candidate in the Department of Critical Studies at California Institute of the Arts. Her work is currently on view at Fundación Botín’s Villa Iris in Spain</description>
                <enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT3P1.mp3" length="40507533" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Thu, 5 Nov 2015 11:49:01 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT III - Part 1: New readings written and given by Maia Nichols, Alex Bovril. </itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT III - Part 1: Maia Nichols and Alex Bovril
LIT LIT LIT LIT III took place at Publication Studio in Vancouver BC on August 2, 2015. New readings were written and given by Ronan Nanning-Watson, Zuzia Juszkiewicz, Bradley
Iles and Ingrid Olauson. Kate Moss’ reading “Swedish Light and Other Poems“ is available as a limited edition chap book, published and distributed by the Somewhat Urgent Series Press. Alex Bovril’s reading comes from his new book “Fragments of Bismuth” a series of short stories  published and distributed by The Somewhat Urgent Series Press. </itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:56:40</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>

<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
        <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT III PART II -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

            <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT III - Part II: Kate Moss and Donato Mancini </title>
                <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT3P2.mp3</link>
                <guid>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT3P2.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Publication Studio: 222 E Georgia St. Vancouver BC - ALEX BOVRIL is a writer and visual artist. Recently, he has been pouring colours of concrete and writing fiction. He is currently an MFA Candidate in Creative Writing at New York University.

DONATO MANCINI makes visual and procedural poetry, bookworks, and visual art. His books and chapbooks include: Snowline (2015), Buffet World (2011) Fact ‘N’ Value (2011), Hell Passport no.22 (2008), Æthel (2007), 58 Free Coffees (2006) and Ligatures (2005). Mancini’s published critical writing includes work on the archive, time and memory in Anamnesia: Unforgetting (2011), and a discourse analysis of poetry reviews in You Must Work Harder to Write Poetry of Excellence (2012). His most recent full length book, Loitersack (2014), is a labyrinthine commonplace book where critical, theoretical and para-literary tendencies intersect in the forms of poetry, poetics, theory, theory theatre, laugh particles and many many questions.

KATE MOSS is an Australian artist who works with drawing, writing, painting, sculpture, sound and performance. Her works explore the possibilities of conversation through the vernacular of landscape, rhythm and material experimentation.

MAIA NICHOLS (b. Berkeley, California) is an artist and writer. She holds a BA in Psychology and a BFA from the University of British Columbia. She is a Masters Candidate in the Department of Critical Studies at California Institute of the Arts. Her work is currently on view at Fundación Botín’s Villa Iris in Spain. </description>
                <enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LIT3P2.mp3" length="23442418" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Thu, 5 Nov 2015 11:50:01 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT III - Part 2: New readings written and given by Kate Moss and Donato Mancini.</itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT III - Part 2: Kate Moss and Donato Mancini
LIT LIT LIT LIT III took place at Publication Studio in Vancouver BC on August 2, 2015. New readings were written and given by Maia Nichols, Alex Bovril, Kate Moss and Donato Mancini. Kate Moss’ reading “Swedish Light and Other Poems" is available as a limited edition chap book, published and distributed by the Somewhat Urgent Series Press. Alex Bovril’s reading is from his new book “Fragments of Bismuth” a series of short stories  published and distributed by The Somewhat Urgent Series Press. </itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:33:48</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>

<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
        <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT VANCOUVER ART BOOK FAIR PART I -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

            <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Book Fair - Part I: Tom Whalen and Emma Metcalfe Hurst  </title>
                <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITVABF1.mp3</link>
                <guid>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITVABF1.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Gallery, 750 Hornby St. Vancouver BC - Tom Whalen and Emma Metcalfe Hurst.
                 </description>
                <enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITVABF1.mp3" length="19850134" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Tue, 8 Dec 2015 11:52:01 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Book Fair - Part 1: New readings written and given by Tom Whalen and Emma Metcalfe Hurst.</itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Book Fair - Part 1: Tom Whalen and Emma Metcalfe Hurst.
LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Book Fair took place at the Vancouver Art Gallery Vancouver BC on October 18th, 2015 as a part of KIOSK: Reading Room. New readings were written and given by Tom Whalen, Emma Metcalfe Hurst, Hugo Noriega and Zuzia Juszkiewicz. Zuzia Juszkiewicz is reading from her new book "PROGRAM", a fifty-six page poem written in 2014 published and distributed by The Somewhat Urgent Series Press.</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:20:41</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>


<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
        <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT VANCOUVER ART BOOK FAIR PART II -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

            <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Book Fair - Part II: Hugo Noriega and Zuzia Juszkiewicz</title>
                <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITVABF2.mp3</link>
                <guid>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITVABF2.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Gallery, 750 Hornby St. Vancouver BC - Hugo Noriega and Zuzia Juszkiewicz.
                 </description>
                <enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITVABF2.mp3" length="21876818" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Tue, 8 Dec 2015 11:52:01 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Book Fair - Part 2: New readings written and given by Hugo Noriega and Zuzia Juszkiewicz.</itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Book Fair - Part 2: Hugo Noriega and Zuzia Juszkiewicz.
LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Book Fair took place at the Vancouver Art Gallery Vancouver BC on October 18th, 2015 as a part of KIOSK: Reading Room. New readings were written and given by Tom Whalen, Emma Metcalfe Hurst, Hugo Noriega and Zuzia Juszkiewicz. Zuzia Juszkiewicz is reading from her new book "PROGRAM", a fifty-six page poem written in 2014 published and distributed by The Somewhat Urgent Series Press. </itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:22:47</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
        <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT IV PART I -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

            <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT IV - Part I: Jacquelyn Ross and Bradley Iles</title>
                <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITIVI.mp3</link>
                <guid>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITIVI.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT IV took place at 221A in Vancouver, BC on December 6, 2015. New readings were given by Jacquelyn Ross, Bradley Iles, Eli Zibin and Steffanie Ling.</description>
                <enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITIVI.mp3" length="36529255" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2015 11:51:02 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT IV - Part 1: New readings written and given by Jacquelyn Ross and Bradley Iles </itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT IV took place at 221A in Vancouver, BC on December 6, 2015. New readings were given by Jacquelyn Ross, Bradley Iles, Eli Zibin and Steffanie Ling.
</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:38:03</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
        <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT IV PART II -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

            <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT IV - Part II: Eli Zibin and Steffanie Ling</title>
                <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITIVII.mp3</link>
                <guid>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITIVII.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT IV took place at 221A in Vancouver, BC on December 6, 2015. New readings were given by Jacquelyn Ross, Bradley Iles, Eli Zibin and Steffanie Ling. </description>
                <enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITIVII.mp3" length="39173450" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2015 11:51:02 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT IV - Part 2: New readings written and given by Eli Zibin and Steffanie Ling </itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT IV took place at 221A in Vancouver, BC on December 6, 2015. New readings were given by Jacquelyn Ross, Bradley Iles, Eli Zibin and Steffanie Ling.
</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:40:48</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
                    <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT SWEET PUP -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

          <item>
              <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT KIOSK LA/BF FUNDRAISER: Emma Metcalfe Hurst and Steffanie Ling</title>
              <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITSWEETPUP.mp3</link>
              <guid>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITSWEETPUP.mp3</guid>
              <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT KIOSK LA/BF took place at Sweet Pup in Vancouver, BC on January 30,2016. New readings were given by Emma Metcalfe Hurst (with assistance from Alyssa Dusevic, Stefana Fratila, Esteban Gonzales, Shizen Jambor, Ellis Sam and Christian Vistan) and Steffanie Ling. </description>
              <enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITSWEETPUP.mp3" length="26332767" type="audio/mpeg" />
              <category>Podcasts</category>
              <pubDate>Sun, 7 Feb 2016 11:52:01 -0500</pubDate>
              <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
              <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
              <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT KIOSK LA/BF FUNDRAISER: Emma Metcalfe Hurst and Steffanie Ling </itunes:subtitle>
              <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT KIOSK LA/BF took place at Sweet Pup in Vancouver, BC on January 30,2016. New readings were given by Emma Metcalfe Hurst (with assistance from Alyssa Dusevic, Stefana Fratila, Esteban Gonzales, Shizen Jambor, Ellis Sam and Christian Vistan) and Steffanie Ling.
              </itunes:summary>
              <itunes:duration>00:27:26</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
          </item>

          <!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
                    <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT 5 -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

          <item>
              <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT V - Catherine de Montreuil, Matea Kulić, Sung Pil Yoon and Marie-Hélène Tessier</title>
              <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITLITLITLITV-2.mp3</link>
              <guid>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITLITLITLITV-2.mp3</guid>
              <description>1. Catherine De Montreuil reading “(Convictions): How I am Queer Because I Got Hetero-Married to my Gay Friend” an homage to Erdem Taşdelen’s “Convictions” 2. Matea Kulić reading from her chapbook “A Case of Arturo” from back to front. 3. Sung Pil Yoon reading “MAKE MAKE AMERICA AMERICA GREAT GREAT AGAIN AGAIN”. 4. Marie-Hélène Tessier performing free-for-all.</description>
              <enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITLITLITLITV-2.mp3" length="140953759 " type="audio/mp3" />
              <category>Podcasts</category>
              <pubDate>Sun, 9 Apr 2017 18:04:03 -0500</pubDate>
              <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
              <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
              <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT V rolled out at the Or Gallery in Vancouver, BC on Sunday, February 21, 2016. Works were presented by Catherine de Montreuil, Matea Kulić, Sung Pil Yoon and Marie-Hélène Tessier.</itunes:subtitle>
              <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT V rolled out at the Or Gallery in Vancouver, BC on Sunday, February 21, 2016. Works were presented by Catherine de Montreuil, Matea Kulić, Sung Pil Yoon and Marie-Hélène Tessier.

                ~

                0:03:00 - Catherine De Montreuil reading “(Convictions): How I am Queer Because I Got Hetero-Married to my Gay Friend” an homage to Erdem Taşdelen’s “Convictions”

00:18:40 - Matea Kulić reading from her chapbook “A Case of Arturo” from back to front

00:36:56 - Intermission Performance

00:39:56 - Sung Pil Yoon reading “MAKE MAKE AMERICA AMERICA GREAT GREAT AGAIN AGAIN”

00:54:32 - Marie-Hélène Tessier performing free-for-all.
              </itunes:summary>
              <itunes:duration>01:13:25</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
          </item>

<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
                    <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT Re-Reading Room -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

          <item>
              <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT VI and ReReading Room - Emma Metcalfe Hurst, Kyla Jamieson, Anahita Jamali Rad and Danielle LaFrance
</title>
              <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITLITLITLITReReadingRoom-2.mp3</link>
              <guid>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITLITLITLITReReadingRoom-2.mp3</guid>
              <description>1. Emma Metcalfe Hurst reading “Speak White Speak What What Speak White Speak,” a bilingual autocorrect translation of Michèle Lalonde’s poem “Speak White” (1967) and Marco Micone’s poetic response “Speak What” (1989)
2. Kyla Jamieson reading some recent poems and 1 of 30 letters to her best friend that suggestively fits into the genre of “epistolary auto-fiction”
3. Anahita Jamali Rad reading two poems-one new, one old-and then some more poems from her new book “For Love and Autonomy” (Talonbooks, 2016)
4. Danielle LaFrance reads two poems: one from her new book “Friendly Fire” (Talonbooks, 2016) and one that she wrote during a time of her life when she was losing her mind again.</description>
              <enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITLITLITLITReReadingRoom-2.mp3" length="168583428" type="audio/mp3" />
              <category>Podcasts</category>
              <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 18:06:03 -0500</pubDate>
              <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
              <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
              <itunes:subtitle>The Vancouver Women’s Bookstore opened in the summer of 1973. We’ve been told it set up shop in an old Victorian house somewhere on Richards Street. Rent was cheap—cheap enough that the Bookstore’s owners could afford to make donations to local women’s centres and other projects they cared about. We heard they lent Ferron (do you know her?) a grand to help her record her first album. From the street you could see the store’s bookshelves, then behind that, up a couple of steps, was a raised area where there was a desk and a few couches. There was coffee and a small library. The walls back there were covered in posters, mostly from a women’s collective in Chicago. We’ve been told that the shelves were stained by the same volunteers who would keep the place running for the next twenty-some years. Three break-ins, a firebombing, and two relocations later, the Bookstore closed in 1996. We haven’t seen pictures but we imagine the shelves were a nice colour.
While doing some archival research this June, Alexandra Bischoff dug up the Vancouver Women’s Bookstore’s inaugural 1973 catalogue. We examined the document as if it were excavated amber. More than just a record of its inventory, the warmly typewritten pages captured the spirit of a community formed during a critical period of intellectual production by and for women. The Bookstore was a setting where individual experience could be elaborated, made material, through social life. The books provided a common language; the shelves, a common space for conversation—between generations, continents. So consider this an invitation to its re-staging. Rereading Room presents a collection of books, documents, and periodicals selected from the titles offered by the Bookstore in its nascent years (1973-1996). Come by, read, maybe talk over coffee; we have a lot to catch up on.
-Vincent Tao, November 2016

ReReading Room can be found at 221a in Vancouver, BC from November 10, 2016-January 14, 2017
http://221a.ca/rereading-room
              </itunes:subtitle>
              <itunes:summary>
                LIT LIT LIT LIT and ReReading Room went down at 221a as a part of ReReading Room programming on Sunday, November 20, 2016 on traditional Coast Salish territory. The evening featured fireside readings by Emma Metcalfe Hurst, Kyla Jamieson, Anahita Jamali Rad and Danielle Lafrance.

                ~

                00:08:47 - Emma Metcalfe Hurst reading “Speak White Speak What What Speak White Speak,” a bilingual autocorrect translation of Michèle Lalonde’s poem “Speak White” (1967) and Marco Micone’s poetic response “Speak What” (1989)

00:24:42 - Kyla Jamieson reading some recent poems and 1 of 30 letters to her best friend that suggestively fits into the genre of “epistolary auto-fiction”

00:46:49 - Anahita Jamali Rad reading two poems-one new, one old-and then some more poems from her new book “For Love and Autonomy” (Talonbooks, 2016)

01:03:42 - Danielle LaFrance reads two poems: one from her new book “Friendly Fire” (Talonbooks, 2016) and one that she wrote during a time of her life when she was losing her mind again.
              </itunes:summary>
              <itunes:duration>01:27:48</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
          </item>

<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
                    <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT VII And Charc 2 -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

          <item>
              <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT VII and Charcuterie 2 - Stacey Ho, Sam Weselowski, Julia Dahee Hong and Sung Pil Yoon</title>
              <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITLITLITLITVII_Charc2.mp3</link>
              <guid>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITLITLITLITVII_Charc2.mp3</guid>
              <description>00:05:42 Stacey Ho (contributor to Charcuterie 2) reads a short text based off of an interview with her aunt, a traditional Chinese medicine practitioner and “Adventures from the Third Bureau,” published in Charcuterie 2.

00:23:41 Sam Weselowski celebrates his first reading by sharing two poems by the American poet Jack Spicer and then follows up with some of his own poems.

00:36:44 Julia Dahee Hong reading about awkward late night pizza transactions and a wool sweater repair by a Master Tailor as documented in her new chap book “A Reasonable Request.”

00:52:26 Sung Pil Yoon (contributor to Charcuterie 2) reads the second text from “The Bus as Hostile Architecture”; a series of five short stories about public transit that will appear consecutively in Charcuterie.
</description>
              <enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITLITLITLITVII_Charc2.mp3" length="94767720" type="audio/mp3" />
              <category>Podcasts</category>
              <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 13:11:04 -0500</pubDate>
              <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
              <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
              <itunes:subtitle>
              </itunes:subtitle>
              <itunes:summary>
                LIT LIT LIT LIT VII took place in conjunction with the magazine launch of Charcuterie 2 on Saturday, April 1 2017 in Spare Room. The evening consisted of readings by Stacey Ho, Sam Weselowski, Julia Dahee Hong and Sung Pil Yoon. Charcuterie is a publication that strives to provide a forum for experimental writing and informed polemics without pedantry. It assembles a polyphony of inquiry and documents the messy landscape of opinion and critique that unravels in close proximity to where we work, live and make art in Vancouver. Visit https://charcuterie.party to learn more.

~

00:05:42 Stacey Ho (contributor to Charcuterie 2) reads a short text based off of an interview with her aunt, a traditional Chinese medicine practitioner and “Adventures from the Third Bureau,” published in Charcuterie 2.

00:23:41 Sam Weselowski celebrates his first reading by sharing two poems by the American poet Jack Spicer and then follows up with some of his own poems.

00:36:44 Julia Dahee Hong reading about awkward late night pizza transactions and a wool sweater repair by a Master Tailor as documented in her new chap book “A Reasonable Request.”

00:52:26 Sung Pil Yoon (contributor to Charcuterie 2) reads the second text from “The Bus as Hostile Architecture”; a series of five short stories about public transit that will appear consecutively in Charcuterie.
              </itunes:summary>
              <itunes:duration>01:05:48</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
          </item>
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
                    <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT III -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

          <item>
              <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT VIII: Nanaimo Edition - Sonnet L’Abbé, Roger Farr, Hamish Hardie, Charlotte Zhang, Casey Wei</title>
              <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITLITLITLITVIII_Nanaimo.mp3</link>
              <guid>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITLITLITLITVIII_Nanaimo.mp3</guid>
              <description>
                00:03:20 - Roger Farr reads “Understanding Understanding Television” a poem about television, “Transitional Demands” a poem that looks at the different syntactical ways “The People” appear via web search, and ends with a long poem based on a psycho-geography mapping of Vancouver.

                00:32:21 - Charlotte Zhang reads her own “Untitled” short story.

                00:43:15 - Sonnet L’Abbé shares a selection of her sonnets from “Sonnet’s Shakespeare” (to be published by Mcclelland and Stewart in 2018) where she writes over all of Shakespeare’s 154 sonnets.

                01:10:49 - Hamish Hardie reads his short story “The Window.”

                01:18:20 - Casey Wei reads “A Letter from the Editor” (her) from the first edition of Agony Klub (AK01), a magazine and mix tape edited by Wei that invites musicians with writing and visual art practices and vice versa to contribute.
</description>
              <enclosure url="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/litlitlitlit/LITLITLITLITVIII_Nanaimo.mp3" length="137566938" type="audio/mp3" />
              <category>Podcasts</category>
              <pubDate>Mon, 5 Jun 2017 21:11:04 -0500</pubDate>
              <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
              <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
              <itunes:subtitle>
              </itunes:subtitle>
              <itunes:summary>
              LIT LIT LIT LIT VIII took a trip to Vancouver Island to host an evening of readings at Nanaimo Art Gallery in Nanaimo, BC on Saturday, May 6 2017. The evening featured poets Sonnet L’Abbé (Nanaimo) and Roger Farr (Gabriola Island) with artist Casey Wei (Vancouver), alongside emerging Code Switching writers Hamish Hardie (Nanaimo) and Charlotte Zhang (Nanaimo).

              ~

              00:03:20 - Roger Farr reads “Understanding Understanding Television” a poem about television, “Transitional Demands” a poem that looks at the different syntactical ways “The People” appear via web search, and ends with a long poem based on a psycho-geography mapping of Vancouver.

              00:32:21 - Charlotte Zhang reads her own “Untitled” short story.

              00:43:15 - Sonnet L’Abbé shares a selection of her sonnets from “Sonnet’s Shakespeare” (to be published by Mcclelland and Stewart in 2018) where she writes over all of Shakespeare’s 154 sonnets.

              01:10:49 - Hamish Hardie reads his short story “The Window.”

              01:18:20 - Casey Wei reads “A Letter from the Editor” (her) from the first edition of Agony Klub (AK01), a magazine and mix tape edited by Wei that invites musicians with writing and visual art practices and vice versa to contribute.

              ~

              This event occurred in conjunction with Art Rock? No.18 on Friday, May 5 2017. Performances by Bye House, CROTCH and DS Lori were hosted at The Black Dot in Nanaimo, BC.

              Special thanks to the City of Nanaimo, Art Lab and Nanaimo Art Gallery for supporting this event.
              </itunes:summary>
              <itunes:duration>01:35:32</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
          </item>
        </channel>
    </rss>
